"use strict";(self.webpackChunkquiz_game=self.webpackChunkquiz_game||[]).push([[293,255],{293:function(e,r,t){t.r(r),t.d(r,{default:function(){return x}});var n=t(885),i=t(791),s=function(){var e=arguments.length>0&&void 0!==arguments[0]?arguments[0]:[],r=arguments.length>1&&void 0!==arguments[1]?arguments[1]:0,t=[],n=[];if(e&&r)for(;t.length<r;)n.push(e.splice(Math.floor(Math.random()*e.length-1),1)[0]),t.push(n.pop());return t},o=[{question:"Who is the main protagonist of Top Gun: Maverick?",id:1,options:[{answer:"Steve Carell",correct:!1,id:11},{answer:"Tom Cruise",correct:!0,id:44},{answer:"Jean-Claude Van Damme",correct:!1,id:33},{answer:"James P. Sullivan",correct:!1,id:22}]},{question:"Which option is a quote from the Fast and Furious franchise?",id:2,options:[{answer:"What a lame franchise",correct:!1,id:11},{answer:"Vin Diesel was born to be bald",correct:!1,id:33},{answer:"Ride or die",correct:!0,id:44},{answer:"Die or ride",correct:!1,id:22}]},{question:"Were Ross and Rachel on a break in Friends TV Series?",id:3,options:[{answer:"How dare u ask that",correct:!1,id:11},{answer:"They were on a breaaaaak",correct:!1,id:33},{answer:"Not really",correct:!1,id:22},{answer:"There is no clear answer to this question to this day",correct:!0,id:44}]},{question:"Is Interstellar movie about interstellar travel?",id:4,options:[{answer:"No, it is about environmental problems",correct:!1,id:11},{answer:"Yes, it mostly is",correct:!0,id:44},{answer:"No, it is about Star Wars",correct:!1,id:33},{answer:"No, it is about Michael Caine being old",correct:!1,id:22}]},{question:"What is the complete name of the Thor movie released in the year 2022?",id:5,options:[{answer:"Thor: Love and I can not be bothered",correct:!1,id:11},{answer:"Thor: Love and Death ",correct:!1,id:33},{answer:"Thor: Love and Thunder",correct:!0,id:44},{answer:"Thor: Love and The Douchebag",correct:!1,id:22}]},{question:"Which movie below is based on a novel?",id:6,options:[{answer:"The Green Mile",correct:!0,id:44},{answer:"Toy story 4",correct:!1,id:11},{answer:"Pitch perfect",correct:!1,id:33},{answer:"Ted",correct:!1,id:22}]},{question:"What did the movie I Am Mother focus on?",id:7,options:[{answer:"A mother",correct:!1,id:11},{answer:"Artificial intelligence",correct:!0,id:44},{answer:"War",correct:!1,id:33},{answer:"Climate change",correct:!1,id:22}]},{question:"Who is batman?",id:8,options:[{answer:"Superman",correct:!1,id:11},{answer:"I think he is Harley Quinn",correct:!1,id:33},{answer:"He is a horse actually",correct:!1,id:22},{answer:"A man dressed as a bat",correct:!0,id:44}]},{question:"Was lightning McQueen the fastest car in the Cars movie released in the year 2006?",id:9,options:[{answer:"No, actually he was the fastest moron",correct:!1,id:11},{answer:"Yes he was",correct:!0,id:44},{answer:"No, Not as fast as Doc Hudson",correct:!1,id:33},{answer:"No, Chick Hicks was",correct:!1,id:22}]},{question:"Hugh Jackman is most famous for what exactly?",id:10,options:[{answer:"Playing as Wolverine",correct:!0,id:44},{answer:"Being a good boy",correct:!1,id:11},{answer:"Playing as Darth vader",correct:!1,id:33},{answer:"Being Australian",correct:!1,id:22}]},{question:"Which movie is not a sci-fi film?",id:11,options:[{answer:"Road To Perdition",correct:!0,id:44},{answer:"Dune",correct:!1,id:11},{answer:"Chappie",correct:!1,id:33},{answer:"12 Monkeys",correct:!1,id:22}]},{question:"Which one in not a member of The Simpson family?",id:12,options:[{answer:"Homer",correct:!1,id:11},{answer:"Marge",correct:!0,id:33},{answer:"Moe",correct:!1,id:44},{answer:"Lisa",correct:!1,id:22}]},{question:"Which one is a famous quote from the joker?",id:13,options:[{answer:"All you care about is chicken nuggies",correct:!1,id:11},{answer:"Let us put a smile on that face",correct:!1,id:33},{answer:"Why so serious",correct:!0,id:44},{answer:"I love you batman",correct:!1,id:22}]},{question:"Did they save Mark Watney at the end of The Martian?",id:14,options:[{answer:"No, they left him to rot there",correct:!1,id:11},{answer:"He was high, so he was not on mars , just high",correct:!1,id:33},{answer:"No they hated him",correct:!1,id:22},{answer:"Yes, yes they did",correct:!0,id:44}]},{question:"Did you like Scarlett Johansson in The Prestige?",id:15,options:[{answer:"No, I hate her in general",correct:!1,id:11},{answer:"meh...",correct:!1,id:33},{answer:"Yes, Chose this option if you want to win the game",correct:!0,id:44},{answer:"No, the hell with her",correct:!1,id:22}]},{question:"Which movie did tom cruise not star in?",id:16,options:[{answer:"Mission: Impossible 1",correct:!1,id:11},{answer:"Mission: Impossible 2",correct:!1,id:33},{answer:"Mission: Possible 4",correct:!1,id:22},{answer:"Mission: Impossible 3",correct:!0,id:44}]},{question:"Chris Evans is most famous for playing as:",id:17,options:[{answer:"Captain America",correct:!0,id:44},{answer:"Captain Italia",correct:!1,id:11},{answer:"Hot guy in in The Nanny Diaries",correct:!1,id:33},{answer:"Some lame movie I do not even remember",correct:!1,id:22}]},{question:"Who is more famous , Chris Hemsworth or Me?",id:18,options:[{answer:"Omg, you are",correct:!1,id:11},{answer:"Chris, Chris is more famous buddy",correct:!0,id:44},{answer:"Takes courage to ask such thing",correct:!1,id:33},{answer:"You can not be serious?",correct:!1,id:22}]},{question:"So , Don't Look Up , what is it about?",id:19,options:[{answer:"It is about boring me to death",correct:!1,id:11},{answer:"Blah blah",correct:!1,id:33},{answer:"It is more than just an asteroid heading towards the earth",correct:!0,id:44},{answer:"meh...",correct:!1,id:22}]},{question:"Which one is not a comic character?",id:20,options:[{answer:"Bruce wayne",correct:!1,id:11},{answer:"Selina kyle",correct:!1,id:33},{answer:"Lex luthor",correct:!1,id:22},{answer:"The real slim shady",correct:!0,id:44}]}],c=10,a=function(){var e=arguments.length>0&&void 0!==arguments[0]?arguments[0]:function(){},r=(0,i.useState)([]),t=(0,n.Z)(r,2),a=t[0],d=t[1],u=(0,i.useState)(!0),l=(0,n.Z)(u,2),h=l[0],m=l[1];(0,i.useEffect)((function(){f()}),[]);var f=function(){m(!0),setTimeout((function(){d(s(o,c)),e(),m(!1)}),1e3)};return{loading:h,result:a}},d=t(176),u=t(561),l=t(184),h=function(e){var r=e.limit,t=e.num,n=e.setNum,s=e.count,o=(0,i.useRef)(),a=function(){return n((function(e){return e<=0?r:e-1}))};return(0,i.useEffect)((function(){return o.current=setInterval(a,1e3),function(){return clearInterval(o.current)}}),[]),(0,i.useEffect)((function(){if(s===c)return n(0),function(){return clearInterval(o.current)}}),[s]),(0,l.jsx)("div",{children:(0,l.jsx)(d.X2,{className:"text-center",children:(0,l.jsx)(u.F,{xs:"12",sm:"4",md:"3",lg:"2",children:(0,l.jsx)(d.Zb,{className:"timer-card",children:(0,l.jsx)(d.eW,{children:(0,l.jsxs)("h4",{className:"timer-num",children:["Timer : ",t]})})})})})})},m=t(324),f=function(e){var r=e.options,t=e.num,o=e.createAnswerModel,c=e.removeOption,a=e.setRemoveOption,u=(0,i.useState)(""),h=(0,n.Z)(u,2),m=h[0],f=h[1],w=(0,i.useState)(r),x=(0,n.Z)(w,2),p=x[0],v=x[1];(0,i.useEffect)((function(){15===t&&f("")}),[t]),(0,i.useEffect)((function(){v(r)}),[r]),(0,i.useEffect)((function(){c&&j()}),[c]);var j=function(){var e=[],r=p.find((function(e){return!0===e.correct})),t=p.filter((function(e){return!1===e.correct})),n=s(t,1);e.push(r),e.push(n[0]),v(e),a(!1)};return(0,l.jsx)("div",{children:(0,l.jsx)(d.eW,{children:p.map((function(e,r){return(0,l.jsx)("div",{className:"cursor--pointer question-text mt-4 question-option ".concat(e.id===m?"option-selected":""),tabindex:"1",onClick:function(){return r=e.id,f(r),void o(r);var r},children:r+1+". "+e.answer})}))})})},w=t(255),x=function(){var e=a(),r=(0,i.useState)(0),t=(0,n.Z)(r,2),s=t[0],o=t[1],x=(0,i.useState)(15),p=(0,n.Z)(x,2),v=p[0],j=p[1],g=(0,i.useState)([]),b=(0,n.Z)(g,2),y=b[0],N=b[1],q=(0,i.useState)(!1),T=(0,n.Z)(q,2),k=T[0],W=T[1],C=(0,i.useState)(!1),S=(0,n.Z)(C,2),I=S[0],M=S[1],F=(0,i.useState)(0),Z=(0,n.Z)(F,2),A=Z[0],D=Z[1],E=(0,i.useState)(!1),H=(0,n.Z)(E,2),L=H[0],X=H[1],R=null;(0,i.useEffect)((function(){e.loading||O()}),[v]),(0,i.useEffect)((function(){10===A&&(R=setTimeout((function(){D(0)}),1e3*v))}),[A]);var O=function(){v===15+A&&s<c&&(o(s+1),D(0))};return(0,l.jsx)("div",{children:e.loading?(0,l.jsx)(m.Z,{}):(0,l.jsxs)(l.Fragment,{children:[(0,l.jsx)("div",{children:s<c?(0,l.jsx)(h,{count:s,num:v,setNum:j,limit:15+A}):(0,l.jsx)(d.X2,{className:"m-auto",children:(0,l.jsx)(u.F,{children:(0,l.jsx)(w.default,{data:e.result,selectedAnswers:y})})})}),s<c&&(0,l.jsx)(d.X2,{className:"d-flex justify-content-center",children:(0,l.jsx)(u.F,{lg:"6",md:"10",children:(0,l.jsx)(d.Zb,{className:"question-card mt-3",children:(0,l.jsx)("div",{children:(0,l.jsxs)(d.eW,{children:[(0,l.jsx)(d.X2,{children:(0,l.jsx)(u.F,{sm:"12",children:(0,l.jsxs)("h4",{className:"question-text",children:[s+1," . ",e.result[s].question," "]})})}),(0,l.jsx)("div",{children:(0,l.jsx)(d.X2,{children:(0,l.jsx)(u.F,{sm:"12",children:(0,l.jsx)(f,{removeOption:k,setRemoveOption:W,num:v,createAnswerModel:function(){var r=arguments.length>0&&void 0!==arguments[0]?arguments[0]:"",t=y,n=e.result[s].id,i=null,o={questionId:n,optionId:r};if(y.length>0&&(i=t.find((function(e){return e.questionId===n}))),i){var c=t.indexOf(i);t.splice(c,1,o)}else t.push(o);N(t)},options:e.result[s].options})})})})]})})})})}),(0,l.jsx)("div",{className:"d-flex justify-content-center",children:s<c&&(0,l.jsxs)(d.X2,{className:"d-flex justify-content-center",children:[(0,l.jsx)(u.F,{xs:"10",sm:"10",md:"12",lg:"12",children:(0,l.jsx)(d.zx,{className:"button-custom mt-2",onClick:function(){j(15),D(0),clearTimeout(R)},children:"Next"})}),(0,l.jsx)(u.F,{xs:"10",sm:"10",md:"6",lg:"6",children:(0,l.jsx)(d.zx,{className:"button-lifeLine mt-2",disabled:I,onClick:function(){W(!0),M(!0)},children:"Remove Two Options"})}),(0,l.jsx)(u.F,{xs:"10",sm:"10",md:"6",lg:"6",children:(0,l.jsx)(d.zx,{className:"button-lifeLine mt-2",disabled:L,onClick:function(){X(!0),D(10),j(v+10)},children:"Add extra 10 seconds"})})]})})]})})}},255:function(e,r,t){t.r(r);var n=t(885),i=t(791),s=t(176),o=t(561),c=t(871),a=t(184);r.default=function(e){var r=e.selectedAnswers,t=(e.data,(0,i.useState)(0)),d=(0,n.Z)(t,2),u=d[0],l=d[1];(0,c.s0)();return(0,i.useEffect)((function(){!function(e){var r=0;e.map((function(e,t){44===e.optionId&&r++})),l(r)}(r)}),[]),(0,a.jsx)("div",{className:"d-flex justify-content-center",children:(0,a.jsx)(s.Zb,{className:"result-card",children:(0,a.jsxs)(s.eW,{children:[(0,a.jsx)("h4",{className:"result-text",children:"Your Result"}),(0,a.jsx)(s.X2,{children:(0,a.jsx)(o.F,{children:(0,a.jsxs)("h4",{className:"result-text",children:["Number of correct answers : ",u]})})}),(0,a.jsx)(s.X2,{children:(0,a.jsx)(o.F,{children:(0,a.jsxs)("h4",{className:"result-text",children:["Number of incorrect answers :"," ",r.length-u]})})}),(0,a.jsx)(s.X2,{children:(0,a.jsx)(o.F,{children:(0,a.jsxs)("h4",{className:"result-text",children:["Number questions unanswered : ",10-r.length]})})}),(0,a.jsx)(s.X2,{className:"d-flex justify-content-center mt-3",children:(0,a.jsx)(o.F,{md:"12",lg:"5",children:(0,a.jsx)(s.zx,{className:"button-custom mt-2",onClick:function(){return window.location.reload(!1)},children:"Try Again"})})})]})})})}}}]);
//# sourceMappingURL=293.584a4fd4.chunk.js.map